devamoney.com 2011-03-24

# Devamoney - Higher and safer tax-free profits!

Home > Privacy Policy

  |  |   **Privacy Policy**  
---|---|---  

We protecting your privacy with secure data management  
---  
  
**Devamoney Ltd.** respects each and every one of our visitors right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. Our Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with a full description of the information we collect about you and what we do with that information. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients as well as our current clients.  
  
In general, you can visit devamoney.com without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we might request that you disclose certain pieces of personal information to us. When you apply for or maintain an account with Devamoney Ltd., we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service. Such information may include:

  * Application Information: Information you provide to us on applications and other forms, such as your name anc country of residence.
  * Transaction Information: Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates as well as information about our communications with you. Examples include your account balances, trading activity, your inquiries and our responses.
  * Verification Information: Information necessary to verify your identity such as a passport or driver's license. Examples also include background information about you we receive from public records. 

|   
  
In addition to personally identifiable information Devamoney Ltd. collects anonymous user information through the delivery of cookies. Cookies allow the Devamoney Ltd. Web site to be more efficient by allowing us to learn what information is important to our visitors, and what isn't. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous. 

A cookie is a small data file that a website stores on your computer's hard disk for the purpose of keeping records when you visit the website. A cookie will not allow a Web site to learn any personally identifiable information unless you have previously disclosed that information to us. The use of cookies is an industry standard and is currently used on most major Web sites. We do not use cookies to retrieve information which was not originally sent in a cookie. We do not use information transferred through cookies for any direct promotional or marketing purposes without your consent.   
  
|   
  
DevamoneyLtd. uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than Devamoney while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our website is secure and that it meets industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data. Devamoney Ltd. shall not be responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of any other person or entity.   
  
|   
  
We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing customer accounts and informing customers about new products and services, and as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates may include companies controlled or owned by us. The information we share with affiliates may include any of the information described above. Our affiliates maintain the privacy of your information to the same extent devamoney.com does in accordance with this Policy.   
  
|    
  
DevamoneyLtd. does not disclose your personal information to third parties, except as described in this Policy. Third party disclosures may include sharing such information with non-affiliated companies that perform support services for your account or facilitate your transactions with Devamoney Ltd., including those that provide professional, legal, or accounting advice to Devamoney Ltd. Non-affiliated companies that assist Devamoney Ltd. in providing services to you are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information to the extent they receive it and to use your personal information only in the course of providing such services and only for the purposes that DevamoneyLtd. dictates. We may also disclose your personal information to third parties to fulfill your instructions or pursuant to your expressed consent. Devamoney Ltd. will not sell your personal information.   
  
|   
  
You may also choose to modify your data on your own initiative by using the " **[EDIT ACCOUNT](http://devamoney.com/394241668@N06)** " page which you will find in the main menu under "Member Menu". If you have any question or concern, please do not hesitate to contact us by email at [**support@devamoney.com**](mailto:support@devamoney.com) .
